<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Radiowave 96.7FM ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Radiowave 96.7FM ]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:30:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wecke & Voigts Group SPAR Survey]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Wecke & Voigts Group SPAR Survey</h1><p>Complete the Wecke & Voigts Group SPAR Survey, and stand a chance to WIN 2 nights accommodation at Grande Rochein Paarl, which includes flights to Cape Town for 2 persons, to the value of N$ 20 000.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3350dca2-f41d-4ddf-8455-359b14fceab2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/complete-thewecke-and-voigts-group-spar-survey-and-stand-a-ch/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8b7ac2c2-ba67-4f2a-ac2d-5ae78fb48f95</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sound for Sight Music Festival]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sound for Sight Music Festival</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6084f7296ee6127e80079743ae734c059983bb55.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/sound-for-sight-music-festival/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6f42eca0-1c28-4cbe-beef-4eb17da5890d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:30:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WhatsApps new encryption may not prove popular with governments ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WhatsApps new encryption may not prove popular with governments </h1><p>Instant messaging service WhatsApp’s move to encrypt its messages shows it’s serious about privacy, but it may run into problems with governments, say experts.   Facebook-owned WhatsApp this week announced that all messages, calls, images and video on its app would be encrypted so that not even WhatsApp employees could see the content. “In practice this means that WhatsApp is now one of the most secure ways to communicate electronically,” said Carey van Vlaanderen, chief executive of ESET Southern Africa. However, some governments may not easily accept encryption of the popular messaging application. India and Saudi Arabia in 2010 and 2012 moved to block BlackBerry’s BBM for its encryption on the grounds of national security. Privacy has also not proved to be very popular with online users.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/97fff658b604d3a805d52cc4d335d80966354d28.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/whatsapps-new-encryption-may-not-prove-popular-with-governme/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">afd56141-567a-44db-aca0-c448ca9a75b8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:29:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Higher Education prioritised in ministry's budget]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Higher Education prioritised in ministry's budget</h1><p>The Ministry of Higher Education, Training and Innovation has identified five programmes to which its share of the 2016/17 National Budget will be allocated.   The Minister said two thirds has been earmarked for operational activities, while the balance is for capital development. The minister said the post-secondary school gap deserves immediate close scrutiny and solutions. “There is an urgent need to increase tertiary education opportunities in Namibia. In this regard, the ministry is looking at different models, with a view to developing a proposal that will be shared with the public, before refinement and submission to Cabinet for approval,” the minister said.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7613f6f9-fb46-4821-bc6e-3d8321d6e9f6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/higher-education-prioritised-in-ministrys-budget/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2015d55-586e-430e-8566-a61b24909e70</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:29:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zuma complains about Justice system]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Zuma complains about Justice system</h1><p>At a meeting with traditional leaders at the House of Traditional Leaders in Pretoria, President Jacob Zuma took a thinly veiled jab at the courts and their system of resolving disputes.   Zuma said  that he would be “very happy that we solve the African problem in the African way, because if we solve them only legally, they become too complicated”. “The law looks at one side only; they do not look at any other thing. They deal with cold facts and I was complaining about that (but) they are dealing with warm bodies, that is the contradiction. I must not talk too much because I might get blamed for something I do not know. I only speak the truth,” he said. This is not the first time Zuma has made reference to the courts and how the African ways of solving things was better.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ba157ca4-1400-4748-a68d-e1219970b1c5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/zuma-complains-about-justice-system/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4c234c1c-30d8-4e19-a128-0d852bb4eccb</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:29:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Katy Perry, Christina Aguilera sign letter calling for changes to copyright law ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Katy Perry, Christina Aguilera sign letter calling for changes to copyright law </h1><p>Hundreds of artists, songwriters, managers, and other players in the music industry are calling on the U.S. Copyright Office to make what they consider to be long overdue changes to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, a law they say is not only out-of-date, but detrimental to artists and the future of the industry.   Katy Perry, Fifth Harmony, Christina Aguilera and Bon Jovi are just some of 57 artists who signed a letter calling for a "sensible reform" of the act, which was signed into law by Bill Clinton in 1998.   "The existing laws — and their interpretation by judges — threaten the continued viability of songwriters and recording artists to survive from the creation of music," the letter reads. "It has allowed major tech companies to grow and generate huge profits by creating ease of use for consumers to carry almost every recorded song in history in their pocket via a smartphone, while songwriters’ and artists’ earnings continue to diminish."  The letter comes just over a week after a report by the Recording Industry Association of America that pointed out an "alarming disparity" between the rise in music consumption and revenue going to artists.   Specifically, they take issue with section 512, or the notice-and-takedown provision. While that may have been effective back when the law was passed in the dial-up era, it's ineffective at best now, since as soon as one illegal video is taken down, another one — or another hundred — is uploaded in its place. In their letter, artists called it "the all-purpose shield that tech companies hide behind while they threaten the livelihood of music creators."      "This outdated law forces us to stand by helplessly as billions of dollars in advertising is sold around illegal copies of our work," the letter reads.   A letter signed by 47 music managers warned that the copyright law's failure to protect creators discourages many young artists from pursuing a music career. They said the core problem of the law is "utter failure of the notice-and-takedown system to keep up with technological innovation and change."     "No one can police that vastness – and anyone who tries to do so finds the universe online is growing faster than our ability to inspect it for illegal copies of our clients’ work. Today, the instant an infringing link is taken down, it is replaced by many more. It’s 'whack-a-mole' on steroids in which every time the mole is knocked down, two more pop up, then four, then eight."  On Dec. 31, the Copyright Office announced a public study of section 512, inviting anyone to send feedback. "While Congress understood that it would be essential to address online infringement as the internet continued to grow, it may have been difficult to anticipate the online world as we now know it, where each day users upload hundreds of millions of photos, videos and other items, and service providers receive over a million notices of alleged infringement."  Comments must be received by 11:59 p.m. Friday.   On Thursday, the Internet Association — whose members include Facebook, Google, Amazon, Pandora, Twitter and more — responded in a statement titled "DMCA Infringement Takedowns Work."      "These smart laws allow people to post content that they have created on platforms - such as videos, reviews, pictures, and text. In essence, this is what makes the Internet great," the statement read. "The safe harbors enable platforms to operate at the scale necessary to create huge benefits for consumers and creators. They have fueled the creation of a booming domestic Internet economy that was worth nearly $1 trillion or 6 percent of GDP in 2014."</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/14f146a9-5e2b-43ed-ab5c-e151bb5dad8d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/katy-perry-christina-aguilera-sign-letter-calling-for-chang/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f2d3e01-2f9a-42d0-b8ae-0cd8dc029c67</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 10:27:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f843da3e910e9614d6af668c1650eb5e3ae1607e.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/5bca81b2-def7-496d-9cd3-4ce4277200ad/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5bca81b2-def7-496d-9cd3-4ce4277200ad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 09:33:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Merle Haggard, country music's outsider hero, dies at 79]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Merle Haggard, country music's outsider hero, dies at 79</h1><p>Merle Haggard, the grizzled country music legend whose songs such as "Okie from Muskogee" and "Fightin' Side of Me" made him a voice for the workingman and the outsider, has died. He was 79. Haggard died Wednesday, his birthday, of complications from pneumonia at his home in Northern California, his agent Lance Roberts told CNN.  Haggard recorded more than three dozen No. 1 country hits in a musical career that spanned six decades, from the 1960s into the 2010s.   He overcame an early life of petty crime and a prison term in San Quentin to develop a rugged, outlaw image that helped sell millions of records.  Tributes immediately began pouring in from the country music world and beyond.  "Country music has suffered one of the greatest losses it will ever experience," said country star Charlie Daniels on Twitter. "Rest in peace Merle Haggard."  "Love and prayers for the Haggard family. Merle was a pioneer ... a true entertainer ... a legend," added Carrie Underwood. "There will never be another like him."  "There are no words to describe the loss & sorrow felt within all of music with the passing of Merle Haggard. Thank God for his life & songs," said singer Brad Paisley.  His longtime friend, Willie Nelson -- with whom Haggard sang "Pancho and Lefty" -- tweeted a simple black-and-white photo with the lines, "He was my brother, my friend. I will miss him."     'The best country singer'  Haggard didn't just sing about the life described in country songs. He lived it.  His father died when Haggard was a child, and he ran away from home and later served time in prison. He drank -- one of his best-known songs is called "I Think I'll Just Stay Here and Drink" -- and partied. He was married five times.  Haggard's song titles were plainspoken and evocative. "I'm a Lonesome Fugitive." "Sing Me Back Home." "Branded Man." "The Bottle Let Me Down." "If We Make It Through December." He may not have written all of his hits, but he sang them with a pure feeling that left no doubt of the pain -- and the joy -- inside.  Despite his advancing age, Haggard maintained a robust touring schedule in recent years. He had canceled a handful of April concerts because of his declining health, and he predicted to his family that his end was near.  "A week ago dad told us he was gonna pass on his birthday, and he wasn't wrong. A hour ago he took his last breath surrounded by family and friends," son Ben Haggard posted on Facebook Wednesday afternoon.  "He loved everything about life and he loved that everyone of you gave him a chance with his music," the younger Haggard wrote. "He wasn't just a country singer.. He was the best country singer that ever lived."</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/defb1ca9-9f8d-4e75-8b29-489bbde10468.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/merle-haggard-country-musics-outsider-hero-dies-at-79/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">31f912ef-7e3d-473e-814b-7464215423f5</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 09:33:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The funniest things fans have compared to Justin Bieber's dread-ful new hairdo]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The funniest things fans have compared to Justin Bieber's dread-ful new hairdo</h1><p>Justin Bieber sure knows how to get attention — good or bad.  The pop star took a break from dominating Vevo views and wooing his ex, Selena Gomez, to attend Sunday night's iHeartRadio Music Awards with a brand new hairstyle: dreadlocks.  He also shared a pic of his bleach blonde tresses on Instagram with a simple caption: "Why."  Why, indeed.  Passionate followers immediately shared their negative reactions, comparing the 'do to creepy Grinch fingers and naked mole rats.  Other outraged followers viewed the new style as cultural appropriation, a criticism the singer also received when he showed off cornrows while on vacation in January.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9e7c42a0-c2e5-4487-af96-2a37d40aeb21.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/radiowave-96-7fm/the-funniest-things-fans-have-compared-to-justin-biebers-dr/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad56a0f0-ea47-4e18-9541-2d2eb6648047</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 09:33:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>